A Guide to the Ellen Glasgow Papers
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #10504
Ellen Glasgow Papers 1874-1945
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
10504
11 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Purchase, 4 May 1982
Container List
- Correspondence
  - Ellen Glasgow to Marian Canby, 1937 Nov 6; ALS, 2 p.
    re: personal matters
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mr. and Mrs. H[enry] S. Canby, 1939 Aug 27; APCS, 1 p.
    contains polite note and greetings
  - Ellen Glasgow to "Dearest Lady" [ Marian Canby], 1940 June 12; ALS, 3 p.
    re Glasgow's health and travel plans
  - Ellen Glasgow to Marian Canby and Henry Canby, 1942 May 8; TLS, 1 p.
    a thank-you letter
  - Ellen Glasgow to Henry Canby, 1943 Mar 2; TLS, 1 p.
    complimenting Mr. Canby on a speech
  - Ellen Glasgow to "Dearest Lady" [ Marian Canby], 1943 Nov 21; TLS, 2 p.
    primarily concerning Glasgow's health
  - Ellen Glasgow to Marian Canby, 1944 Feb 24; TLS, 3 p.
    re her personal feelings for Mrs. Canby
  - Ellen Glasgow to Marian Canby, 1944 Apr 12; TLS, 3 p.
    details Glasgow's response to Mrs. Canby's poetry along with other personal concerns
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. [Marian] Canby, n. d.; ALS, 3 p.
    re personal matters
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. [Marian] Canby, n. d.; ALS, 2 p.
    thank-you letter
  - Christmas card from Ellen Glasgow, unsigned, n. d.